<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Tool living</title>
  <subtitle>recommend the best tool</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://www.toolliving.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-07-17T14:25:10.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://www.toolliving.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>ToolLiving</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>SendAnywhere - Free full platform file sharing tool</title>
    <link href="https://www.toolliving.com/2017/07/18/SendAnywhere-Free-full-platform-file-sharing-tool/"/>
    <id>https://www.toolliving.com/2017/07/18/SendAnywhere-Free-full-platform-file-sharing-tool/</id>
    <published>2017-07-18T13:33:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-17T14:25:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I recently discovered this easy to use professional platform sharing tool: <a href="https://send-anywhere.com/" target="_blank" rel="external">SendAnywhere</a>. Perhaps its transmission capability is as good as its name.</p>
<p>Cross-platform transmission and sharing tools are many, Android has <a href="https://sspai.com/app/AirDroid" target="_blank" rel="external">AirDroid</a>, <a href="https://sspai.com/app/Pushbullet" target="_blank" rel="external">Pushbullet</a>, iOS can also use Pushbullet. Unfortunately, AirDroid only for the Android system services, Pushbullet need to log through the Google account, the transmission of large files worrying.</p>
<h2 id="Covering-the-entire-platform-of-the-client"><a href="#Covering-the-entire-platform-of-the-client" class="headerlink" title="Covering the entire platform of the client"></a>Covering the entire platform of the client</h2><p>For a file transfer software, the supported platform is very important, directly affecting the number of devices available for use and transmission.Similar to other file transfer software, you need to install a client before you want to use SendAnywhere. And SendAnywhere coverage is very wide, can be regarded as a full platform.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/bRSaKNq.png" alt="SendAnywhere supports full platform clients"></p>
<ul>
<li>Mobile has a regular iOS, Android, Windows Phone, and even provides a Kindle version</li>
<li>Desktop side is Windows (UWP and Win32 version), macOS, Linux version, also provides the Outlook plug-in.</li>
<li>Web page has a web version, Chrome extension, Chrome app, Office 365 Outlook web page plugin, also opened the Wordpress plugin, Slack plugin, Gmail plugin, and provided to other browsers API.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="Key-two-dimensional-code-link-share-files-everywhere"><a href="#Key-two-dimensional-code-link-share-files-everywhere" class="headerlink" title="Key, two-dimensional, code link, share files everywhere"></a>Key, two-dimensional, code link, share files everywhere</h2><p>SendAnywhere in terms of sharing can be said to be another way.There are three ways to share: “6-digit key”, “two-dimensional code sharing” and “sharing link”.</p>
<h2 id="Speed-transmission-and-quick-sharing-with-data-to-speak"><a href="#Speed-transmission-and-quick-sharing-with-data-to-speak" class="headerlink" title="Speed transmission and quick sharing, with data to speak"></a>Speed transmission and quick sharing, with data to speak</h2><p>As the network conditions are different, I own the actual experience for everyone to make a reference.</p>
<p>I use the 6-bit key to share the form, in the LAN environment from the iPhone to the PC directly to the transmission of 79 photos, a total of 151 MB, time-consuming 16 seconds. The average speed of 9.43 MB / s, with two-dimensional code to share the effect is the same.</p>
<p>I use the 6-bit key to share the form, in the 4G environment from the iPhone to the PC to transmit 151 MB of photos, time-consuming 32 seconds, the average speed of 4.71 MB / s. This can also be seen as “through 6-bit key to share to friends” simulation test.</p>
<p>I use the link to share the way, the same transmission 151 MB of photos. IPhone side upload takes 2 minutes and 45 seconds, the average speed of 0.92 MB / s. Received in the computer side of the file, download time 36 seconds, the average speed of 4.19 MB / s. This data depends on the upstream and downstream network speed, may be different.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/A4F2emw.png?1" alt="Transfer the photo of the experiment, the picture shows the Windows client">)</p>
<p>Through the results of this experiment summed up some of the experience, the dry goods posted for your reference:</p>
<ul>
<li>In the backup photo to the computer, the preferred use of 6-bit key form, the speed can reach the full speed of the network transmission.</li>
<li>In a short time (10 minutes) to share with friends, it is recommended to choose 6 key transmission, the speed is quite fast. Depending on the slower side of the two sides.</li>
<li>If the two sides of the network speed is not equal (one very slow), it is recommended to select the link to share.</li>
<li>A short period of time the other party can not receive, then select the link to share, the file will be stored on the server for 48 hours.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="Beyond-the-sharing-of-local-area-network-regardless-of-network-disk-restrictions"><a href="#Beyond-the-sharing-of-local-area-network-regardless-of-network-disk-restrictions" class="headerlink" title="Beyond the sharing of local area network, regardless of network disk restrictions"></a>Beyond the sharing of local area network, regardless of network disk restrictions</h2><p>There are a lot of file transfer software is the limitations of “local area network”, file sharing software is usually limited (such as a single file size, video format, etc.), and these are precisely the advantages of SendAnywhere.</p>
<p>The above mentioned several sharing operations are not limited to <code>local area network</code>. Again, not limited to <code>local area network</code>.</p>
<ul>
<li>With 6-bit key sharing, you can directly transfer between the two devices are not suitable for the existence of important files within the network disk.</li>
<li>Use the link to share, it means that your friends can not download this software, you can directly open the link to download.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="Information-age-to-share-files-safety-first"><a href="#Information-age-to-share-files-safety-first" class="headerlink" title="Information age to share files, safety first"></a>Information age to share files, safety first</h2><p>The security of file transfers is also an important factor in our choice of transferring software, especially if the link sharing to the server needs to be compromised.</p>
<ul>
<li>File transfer using the 6-digit key transfers files directly between the two devices, and does not store files on the server. So you do not have to worry about file leaks.</li>
<li>For link sharing and send to device, files are uploaded to the server temporarily. All files are encrypted and stored to protect against external attacks and spills. Stored files are automatically deleted from the server after expiration. At the time of transmission, the file is encrypted and transmitted so that the contents of the file being transferred can not be known by others.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="Summary"><a href="#Summary" class="headerlink" title="Summary"></a>Summary</h2><p>In the file transfer and sharing, SendAnywhere only full platform and free client download files these two conscience function can go beyond many similar software.</p>
<p>SendAnywhere provides the idea of sharing files, that is, through the network disk, directly transfer files between devices. The benefits of this are very obvious, we do not have to worry about the file was leaked, do not have to worry about the contents of the third party to see.</p>
<p>Also due to network speed constraints, I do not think the current file transfer tool can completely replace the data lines, but excellent file transfer software can still save us a lot of time and the trouble of plugging data lines, especially in the backup photos, SendAnywhere Also provides the option to “back up all photos”, which is not lost to the data line experience.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;I recently discovered this easy to use professional platform sharing tool: &lt;a href=&quot;https://send-anywhere.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;exte
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="File" scheme="https://www.toolliving.com/categories/File/"/>
    
    
      <category term="File" scheme="https://www.toolliving.com/tags/File/"/>
    
      <category term="Share" scheme="https://www.toolliving.com/tags/Share/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
